麦克斯 第二桌的小费你收了吗
Max, did you pick up the tip from table two?
没 但我蛮确定"受"了葡萄球菌感染
No, but I'm pretty sure I picked up a staph infection.
所以"九牛一毛 不成敬意"就真的给一毛钱
So they literally gave me their two cents worth.
这也太丢人
This is so embarrassing,
钱上的林肯总统都不敢看我了
even Abe Lincoln won't make eye contact.
姑娘们 我需要你们帮我做件事
Girls, I need you to do something for me.
规矩你懂 不能跟任何"帮"你
You know the rule: nothing for you,
在你身上 你附近 或我们里有关
on you, near you, or in us.
我要去厕所 帮我看着厨房
I'm going to restroom. Keep eye on the kitchen.
我有个蛋在四分钟后好
I have a four-minute egg and a five-minute date
可我跟杂志泳装特辑有个五分钟约会
with the Sports Illustrated Swimsuit Issue.
你看到的东西跟我的一样吗
Hey, do you see what I see?
起火吗
A fire?
不 是逃离这工作的机会
No, a way out of this job.
天啊 起火啦
Lord Jesus, there's a fire.
你们俩要去处理吗
You two gonna do anything about that?
反正我是没打算去
'Cause I'm not.
我不跟火或是基督教长老会的人斗
I don't mess with fire or Presbyterians.
火 起火啦
Fire, fire!
我闻到火烧的味道
I smell fire!
别干坐着啊 快做点什么啊
Well, don't just stand there. Do something!
我们有啊
We are.
烤棉花糖
S'mores!
真没想到你会想这里被烧成废墟
You'd think you want this place to burn to the ground.
真没想到你会这么想
You'd think that.
卡洛琳 做点什么啊
Caroline, do something.
包我身上
I'm on it.
加巧克力吗
Chocolate?
阿憨 别这么靠近
Han, not too close.
你不知道靠太近 韩国烧烤的味道
You know you can never get the smell of Korean barbecue
会弄不掉吗
out of your clothes.
刚才那幕不是他灭了火
Either he put the fire out,
就是这个小机器人射了
or that little robot just had an orgasm.
欢迎来到嗨翻天甜点吧
Welcome to The High dessert bar.
我是迎宾员兼半经理
I'm the hostess slash quasi-manager.
第一天刚来时 就被大大提拔了
First day in, got a huge promosh.
我不想炫耀
I hate to brag,
但当时连"狂拽酷炫"这词都用上了
but the word "dazzling" was used.
是你自己说的吧
Yeah, by you.
这屁点般的权力真把你冲昏了头
Little to no power has really gone to your head.
对啊
It has.
她就像是烘焙界的普京
She's like the Putin of pastry.
知道自己不光是在
But doesn't it feel good
那个餐厅工作 不会很开心吗
to not just be working at the diner?
我一整天都没有踩到婴儿尿布滑倒呢
I haven't slipped on one used baby diaper all day.
说到婴儿
Speaking of babies,
看 阿憨在那里
look, there's Han.
这大概是第三次
That's, like, the third time
我抓到他在暗中监视我们了
I caught him spying on us.
他为什么要跟踪他最烂的两个员工啊
Why would he stalk two of his worst employees?
是啊 就像是威利在哪里游戏
I know. It's like Where's Waldo?
可是你一直看到威力
When you don't want to find Waldo.
没看到迎宾员在这里哦
Not seeing a hostess up in here.
她是在说半经理
She meant quasi-manager.
如果哪天马丁·斯科塞斯走进来
If Marty Scorsese walks in here,
你会想他自己给自己找座吗
do you want him to seat himself?
他会走丢的 走丢[输]
He'll be lost. Lost.
抱歉 乔 我刚才在给麦克斯...
Sorry, Joe, I was just over there giving Max--
亲 如果我想听故事
Honey, I'll download an audiobook
我会去下载有声书
if I want to hear a story.
我想带你认识一个人
I want you to meet someone.
我也想啊 等时候到了 我会的
Me too, and I'm sure I will when the time is right
我也能接受相亲
and I'm open to it.
但我现在想先冲刺事业
Kind of focusing on me right now.
停
Stop.
学会察言观色好吗
Learn to read faces.
我的重点又不是你
I'm not talking about you.
我的重点是他好吗
I'm talking about him.
你好 很高兴认识你
Hello, pleasure to meet you.
我叫纳西特
I'm Nashit.
纳西特是印度名字呢
Nashit's an Indian name,
可是你的口音不是爱尔兰的吗
and isn't that an Irish accent I detect?
还是你的牙太白了把我闪晕了
Or have I just lost consciousness from how white your teeth are?
的确
Yes, it is.
我爸是印度人 我妈是爱尔兰人
My father's Indian. My mother's Irish.
他又是爱尔兰人 又是印度人
He's Irish. He's Indian.
他就是东西合一
He's East meets West.
他就是爱尔兰酒精咖啡加男子组合的
He's everything in a hot Irish coffee,
豪华大礼包
boy band package.
我在大街上的一张脏椅子旁发现了他
I found him on the street next to a dirty chair.
你好 我叫卡洛琳
Hi, I'm Caroline,
嗨翻天的迎宾员兼半经理
the hostess slash quasi-manager at The High.
你是嗑药嗨了吗
Are you high?
你的话实在是多到不行
'Cause that was a lot of talking.
这是谁 我可以上哪也整一个
Who is this, and where can I get one?
他是纳西特 我们的新服务员
This is Nashit, our new waiter.
很高兴见到你
Oh, it's lovely to meet you.
你能说"可口到有魔性"吗
Can you say "magically delicious"?
我真的希望纳西特能成功
I really want Nashit to work out.
我喜欢颜值高的人获得成功
I like it when good-looking people succeed.
那对我真是好消息啊
Well, I guess that's good news for me.
是咩
Is it?
亲爱的
Hi, honey.
见过我们的新服务员了吗
Have you met the new waiter?
我好爱他 他是我的小亲亲
I love him. He's my favorite.
如果我搞男人 那他已经被我搞到精尽人亡了
If I did men, he would've been done by now.
你觉得你很漂漂咩
Hmm, so you think you're pretty.
奴家也觉得
Well, I do too.
纳西特 你听好了
Okay, Nashit, pay attention.
这些是餐桌 这里是甜品吧台
These are the tables. This is the dessert bar.
而这是我的海咪咪
And these are my boobs.
麦克斯 专业一点好吗
Max, be professional.
这是我的海咪咪哦 先生
These are my boobs, sir.
别闹了 我要教他做服务员
Please, I have to make him a waiter.
行 你教他做服务员
Fine, you make him a waiter,
晚点我教他做爱
and I'll just make him later.
给 这不是你们点的 对吧
Here you go. This isn't yours, is it?
不是 因为人家已经吃过甜点了
No, because they already have dessert.
靠
Damn it.
你是不是一个小时前跟我要过水
You asked for water, like, an hour ago, didn't you?
真是太对不起了
I'm so sorry.
嘴唇干一点也没事啦 别担心
Oh, don't you worry those lips.
而且我们还有一辈子要过 一小时又算什么
And what's an hour when we have our whole lives ahead of us?
麦克斯 我都不知道该怎么办了
Max, I don't know what I'm gonna do.
我服务员干得太差了
I stink as a waiter.
差到无可救药
This is desperate.
这种时候服用一记麦式亲热便能化解
Well, desperate times call for us making out.
我有个问题想问你
Hey, I have a question for you.
你的皮肤又白又嫩
Your skin is so creamy and white.
你体内有小小的爱尔兰品种吧
You must have a little Irish in you.
我体内有过好多小小爱尔兰"种"
I've had a lot of little Irishes in me.
你是在开黄腔 对吧
That's meant to be dirty, right?
我的意思只指你挺漂亮的
Well, I just mean that I think you're quite beautiful.
那我的话是指我们"搞"定了
Oh, well, then I just mean we're doing it.
我曾以为世上没有人
I did not think there was somebody
鼻子比我好看 或比我更次的服务员了
who had a prettier nose or was worse than me waiting tables,
但现在有了
but here we are.
纳西特 现在外面一只叉子都没有
Nashit, there's not a fork in the mix out there.
快出去叉那些女人去
Now, get out there and fork those women.
别给他这么大压力
Take it easy on him.
我可不想他在"叉"我前
I don't him to be all forked out
就"叉"尽人亡了
by the time he gets to me.
我要在我床上跟纳西特搞到
I'm gonna have so much sex on my bed with Nashit
我得买新的床单[西特]
that I'm gonna need a new sheet.
你这不是老牛吃嫩草吗
Aren't you too old for him?
是啊 可是测验说我心理年龄只有14岁啊
Yeah, but that test said mentally I'm 14,
所以我们绝对有"搞"头
so we can totally do it.
我要去唐人街找人帮我扎针
Well, I'm off to Chinatown to have someone put needles in me.
天啊 我好喜欢你的外套
Oh, my God. I love your coat.
看起来也太美了
You look gorgeous.
那整个气场
I mean, the way it flows.
好吧 我能看出来你是个马屁精
Okay, so I can see you're a kiss-ass,
所以听好了
so here's the thing.
做为我的半经理
As my quasi-manager,
或是其他你唬烂别人的头衔
or whatever nonsense you're telling people,
我要你去让麦克斯与纳西特消消欲火
I need you to tell Max and Nashit to cool it.
嗨翻天不准有员工炮情
There are no hookups here at The High.
妥了 另外我们也可以不称"半"啊
Done, and we can stop staying "quasi"
只要我们俩都同意让我当经理的事
if we're both on board with the manager thing.
没这回事
We're not.
嗨翻天的主题是高档糕点
The High is about fine pastry,
而不是某人肮脏龌龊的感情生活
not someone's sordid love life.
但讽刺的是 我需要你帮忙
And in an ironic twist, I need you to kick
把我女朋友火辣的屁屁踹出店外
my girlfriend's hot ass out of here
如果她有来的话
if she comes in.
给你一百
Here's $100.
一百大洋呢
That's $100.
放心 她的热辣小屁屁已经被踹飞了
Consider her hot ass out the door.
我们在吵架
We're in a fight.
她喝醉酒 偷了我的黑卡
She got drunk, stole my Black Card,
给90人买了高档餐厅的汤
and bought 90 people soup at Barney Greengrass,
更何况那家的汤根本就不好喝
and the soup isn't even good there.
我没有要拒绝你 我可想要这钱了
Do not take this as a no, because I want the money,
但你为什么不自己跟她说呢
but why can't you just tell her yourself?
我不能自己说啊
I can't tell her myself.
她比我小
She's younger than me,
大家都懂伴侣变成妈之后 实在很没情趣
and everyone knows the mommy thing just isn't sexy.
记得确保她有吃东西 然后安全到家
Make sure she eats something and gets home safe.
卡洛琳 我有个问题问你
Caroline, I have a question for you.
那些女人递给我的纸条 我该怎么处理
What do I do with the notes the women give me?
你都收到纸条啦
You've gotten notes?
有几张
Just a few.
这些女人怎么能饥渴到这程度
How could women be this desperate?
麦克斯 这张是你写的
Max, this one's from you.
大多数都是我写的
They're mostly all from me,
除了那些商业名片
except the business card.
老娘才不需要一张破卡片
I don't need no damn card
来表示我专门从事"伤"风败俗"业"
to let him know I'm all business.
麦克斯 乔说店里不许有员工炮情
Max, Joe just told me there are no hookups at The High,
但从你画的这张细节满满的图来看
and judging from this very detailed picture you drew,
你摆明就是有此计划
that's exactly what you're planning.
我的计划可不止这样 只是没纸画了
Oh, I was planning more. I just ran out of paper.
我们不能失去这里的工作
We can't lose these jobs.
我手握两张百元大钞 而且我快忍不住
I have two $100 bills, and I'm this close
要加入亚马逊高级会员了[年费99美金]
to pulling the trigger on an Amazon Prime account.
亚马逊高级会员
Amazon Prime?
权力真是把你冲昏头了啊
You have been driven mad with power.
新鲜 洒满糖霜的糕点
Fresh, flakey pastry.
说到洒满
And speaking of flakes,
乔的傻蛮女友来了
there's Joe's flakey girlfriend.
有人能帮忙让这椅子别缠着我外套了吗
Can someone help me get my chair off my coat?
她怎么进来的
How did she get in here?
乘着七彩药云飘进来的吧
Probably floated in on a cloud of Valium.
"滚时" 就是她滚蛋的时候到了
It's go time, as in she's got to go.
挪走火车残骸比赶这"失智残孩"容易
You have a better chance moving an actual train wreck,
但还是祝你马到成功
but good luck.
艾莉 你好 你...
Allie, hi, you--
艾莉 你好
Allie, hi.
-你得... -抱歉
- You need-- - Sorry.
我还在宿醉 头好疼
But I am hungover, and I have a headache.
能来杯拿铁 配上大麻吗
Could I get a latte with a side of weed?
不行 这里又不是阿姆斯特丹
No, because this isn't Amsterdam
或比尔·马赫的家里
or Bill Maher's house.
你得离开这里
Now, you need to leave.
你知道乔不喜欢你在店里
You know Joe doesn't want you in here.
我不走
Well, I'm not leaving.
我的腿不能动
My legs won't move
因为我嗑的肌肉松弛剂开始作用了
because my muscle relaxers just kicked in.
强哥 能帮我个忙吗
John, can you do me a favor?
把艾莉请出去
Walk Allie outside,
请出去是指 把她抱起来
and by that, I mean pick her up
扛着她出去
and carry her outside.
人家上的是糕点学校
I went to pastry school.
又不是史莱克
I'm not Shrek.
当然不是啦 你比较像费安娜
Of course not. You're much more Fiona.
妹子真会说话
Girl, that's good.
我本来要说驴子 因为我跟它屁屁都很翘
I was gonna say the donkey, 'cause I have a fine ass.
好吧 行
Okay, fine.
司机 去两地方 高档百货跟冻酸奶店
Driver, two stops. Barney's and fro-yo.
厄尔 我们又迟到了 有保住我们小命吗
Earl, we're late again. Did you keep us alive?
麦克斯 我连自己的小命都保得勉强了
Max, I can barely keep myself alive.
今早我的心脏需要电击
This morning, I had to jump-start my heart
我自己得手指插进插座里
by putting my finger in the socket
来一场《猫和老鼠》般的触电
Tom and Jerry style.
你们好呀
Oh, hello.
你们俩今天都干嘛了
So what did you girls do today?
昨晚在此分别后 我就再也没见过你们了
I haven't seen you since right here last night.
真的吗 阿憨
Oh, really, Han?
我发誓我可是见你在甜点吧附近鬼鬼祟祟
'Cause I swear I saw you lurking around outside The High.
要么是你
It was either you,
要么就是皮卡丘来纽约玩了
or Pikachu is visiting New York.
你这话完全伤不到我
That one barely grazed me,
因为我来自韩国
because I'm Korean,
皮卡丘来自日本
and Pikachu is Japanese.
你一点也不了解《口袋妖怪》
You don't know anything about Pokemon.
阿憨 你或许不是来自日本
Han, you may not be Japanese,
但未来 你肯定会被"男人搞"[口袋妖怪]
but in the future, you're definitely gonna be poked by a mon.
那就是你
And it was you.
不 不是我
No, it was not.
-就是 -不是
- Yeah, it was. - Wasn't.
- Was. - Wasn't.
-不是 -就是 不是
- Wasn't. - Was--wasn't.
英语不是我的母语
English is my second language.
承认吧 你吃醋了
Admit it, you're jealous
因为我们在另一家餐厅工作
we're spending time with another restaurant.
我才没有吃醋呢
I am not jealous.
-你有 -没有
- Are so. - Am not.
-没有 -我有 没有
- Am not. - Are so--not.
你要逼死谁呀
Oh, my God!
卡洛琳 你他妈这是在干嘛
Caroline, what the hell are you doing?
我在闻百元大钞啊
I'm smelling a $100 bill.
这是我的小三餐厅赏的
It's from my other restaurant.
让我拿去买好东西
It buys me nice things.
醋意大发了吗
Jealous?
你无依无靠时 是我收留了你
I took you in when you had no one.
你好 可以帮我个忙吗
Hi, can you help me?
我想找麦克斯
I'm looking for Max.
为什么 你好呀
Why, hello.
现在喜欢男人会不会太晚了
Is it too late to be gay?
纳西特
Nashit?
天啊 就连在停尸房的灯光下 他都这么帅
Oh, my God, he even looks good here in morgue light.
我们一定要开搞
We are so doing it.
卡洛琳 你把手机忘在餐厅的桌子上了
Caroline, you left your phone on the table at the restaurant.
我承认 我用这个当借口
I confess, I used it as an excuse
就为了来见麦克斯
to come and see Max.
这手机不是我的 是乔的女朋友的
This isn't mine. It's Joe's girlfriend's.
我没有iPhone 6
I don't have an iPhone 6.
我只有一部iPhone 瘤
I have an iPhone sick.
扌亠口冂口 我
D-O-I-N-G it!
麦克斯 为什么纳西特会来这
Max, why is Nashit here?
因为这是上帝欠我的
Because God owes me.
你不会真的喜欢他吧
You can't seriously be into him.
他看起来就像某个男子乐队的成员
He looks like someone in a boy band.
是啊 他要去"一个方向"[单向组合]
Yeah, and he's going one direction...
就是我下面的方向
Down there.
但如果你跟他睡了
But if you sleep with him,
那纳西特就屎到临头了
then Nashit is gonna hit the fan.
而且你怎么知道你喜不喜欢他
How do you know you even like him?
你知道我喜欢什么吗 跟他开搞
You know what I like? That we're doing it.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我刚被一辆计程车撞了
I just got hit by a cab,
天啊 现在我特别想吃蟹腿
and, boy, am I in the mood for crab legs.
你有一个优点 宝贝
The thing about you, baby--
"撞"你再多次 你始终屹立不摇
you bounce back from a good pounding
夜夜如此
every single night.
等等
Wait a minute.
那是我的卡座
That's my booth.
很高兴见到你
Oh, it's lovely to meet you.
啥
What?
你那是啥鬼地方的口音啊
What the hell kind of accent is that?
我来自爱尔兰
I'm from Ireland.
什么
What?
麦克斯 你们不许开搞
Max, you are not doing it.
-行 -不行
- Are. - Not.
-不行 -拜托 我可是沃顿毕业的
- Not. - Please, I went to Wharton.
听着 我们应该去你住的地方开搞
Look, we should go to your place when we do it
这样搞的时候卡洛琳才不会在旁边碍事
so that Caroline won't be there while we're doing it.
好啊 可我才来美国两天
Lovely, but I just came to America two days ago.
我没有住的地方
I have no place to go.
事实上
In fact,
我之前一直睡在乔说的那张脏椅子上
I've been sleeping on that dirty chair Joe spoke of.
我靠
What?
他是在唱歌吗
Is he singing?
我的老天
Oh, my God.
他又帅又无家可归
He's gorgeous and homeless?
那可是你的梦中情人啊
That's your dream guy.
命中注定我搞他
We are so doing it!
这简直不可能嘛
Ugh, this is impossible.
感觉像在帮珍爱塞进奥斯卡礼服
I feel like I'm putting an Oscar dress on Precious.
我在给纳西特铺沙发呢
I'm making up the couch for Nashit.
你真是太贴心了
That is so nice of you.
等我们搞完后 他得有个地方睡觉
He's gonna need a place to crash after we have sex.
不 不许再提这茬
No, that's off the table.
真不敢相信你居然邀他来家里住
I can't believe you invited him to stay here.
我也不敢相信你居然拒绝去星巴克过夜
And I can't believe you refused to sleep at Starbucks tonight
不给我们留点私人空间
to give us some privacy.
况且 你也喜欢诺拉·琼斯不是吗
I mean, you like Nora Jones.
麦麦好喜欢
Max likey.
-麦克斯 听着 -不 你给我听着
- Max, listen. - No, you listen.
老娘买不起糖 所以他这甜头我吃定了
I can't afford candy, so he has got to be it.
谢谢让我在你们家洗澡
Thanks for the shower.
天啊 他的肌肉直指他的"鸡肉"
Oh, no, his muscles point to his penis.
麦克斯 别再敲了
Max, stop with the banging.
只要你还欲火焚身 我就不会放你出来
I'm not letting you out while you're still in heat.
那不是我敲的
It's not me.
我在列一千种杀死你的方法
I'm making a list of ways to kill you!
我觉得我就像一个大麻烦
I feel like I'm being a bother,
我还觉得我身子下压到了一根大麻烟斗
and I think I'm sleeping on a bong.
开门
Open up.
我知道里面什么情况
I know what's going on in there.
天啊
Oh, my God.
那是乔的声音
That's Joe.
她肯定发现你和麦克斯勾搭上了
She must've found out about you and Max hooking up.
不是吧
Oh, no.
麦克斯 乔来了
Max, Joe is here.
快用你平时
You need to do that thing you do
把人从走廊吓走的那招
to scare people out of the hallway.
你想用哪招 看门狗
What do we think, guard dog
还是视力不好子弹上膛的老太婆
or little old lady with poor eyesight and loaded gun?
好吧 我走
Fine, I'm going.
所以我从来不愿离开曼哈顿
This is why I never leave Manhattan.
你要进那俩姑娘的公寓吗
Hey, you need to get in the girls' apartment?
我有钥匙
I have a key.
我找找我的大包包哈
Find it here in my big bag.
肯定在包包里某处
I know it's in here somewhere.
我找到了润唇膏
Well, I got the lip balm.
我找到...瞧 我找到了《圣经》
I got--Oh, look, I got the Holy Bible.
我找到了...
I got--
瞧 卫星电视的遥控器
Oh, look. Oh, the DirecTV remote.
天啊 我的雌性激素要被耗没了
Oh, my God, I'm losing estrogen.
麦克斯 你和纳西特躲进你房间
Max, you and Nashit go hide in your room,
但不许做爱
but no sex.
你听见啦 她说不许做爱
You heard her, no sex,
所以做什么都行但... 全都行哦
so everything but, and I mean everything,
但除了那个
and I mean but.
找到了 就在...
Oh, here it is. It's right--
原来一直就在冷盘肉下面
It was right under the cold cuts the whole time.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
你好呀 乔
Hey. Hi, Joe.
对嘛
Yeah.
对嘛 怪不得把头发剪短了
Yeah, the shorter hair makes sense now.
我就说嘛
Yeah.
好样的 卡洛琳
Good for you, Caroline.
希望你会喜欢又长又无聊的故事
I hope you like long, boring stories.
好了 艾莉在哪里 我知道她在这
Okay, where's Allie? I know she's here.
我在她手机装了个间谍软件
I put a spy app on her phone,
虽然此举并不光荣 但我是一个嫉妒心强的女人
and I'm not proud of it, but I'm a jealous woman.
她的手机呀 在我这呢
Oh, her phone. I have it.
今天我按照您的吩咐 把她踢出店里时
She left it at The High when I threw her ass out today
她把手机落那里了
per your instructions.
真不知道一开始
I don't know how I thought this thing
我怎么会觉得我俩能在一起
was gonna work out to begin with.
我们在科切拉音乐节上相遇
We met at Coachella.
我们俩都在"吃"迷幻药[莫莉]
We were both on Molly,
这位超级性感的菲律宾女孩
this intensely hot Filipino girl.
我听到寻欢作乐的声音
I'm hearing sexual sounds.
以及秘密羞愧的暗号从卧室传出
And hints of secret shame coming from the bedroom.
-艾莉在里面 -不 里面没人
- Allie is here. - No, no one's here.
那是我们的白噪音助眠器
That's just our white noise machine.
我无语了 你都不是她喜欢的型
I'm shocked. You're not even her type.
你的嘴唇薄得像两道签字笔画的线
Your lips are like two flair-pen marks.
场面真火辣
That's hot.
拜托不要解雇纳西特
Please don't fire Nashit!
苏斯博士的高帽是我的主意
The Dr. Seuss hats were my idea.
我们在玩《在老爸身上跳来跳去》
We were playing Hop on Pop.
我是老爸
I was Pop.
我都不知道里面还有个男的
I didn't even know there was a boy in there.
我只看见你
I only saw you.
但嗨翻天有规定 员工之间不能有炮情
Okay, since there are no hookups at The High,
如果你不立刻停止跟他上床
if you don't stop sleeping with him immediately,
我的新经理
my new manager...
卡洛琳
Caroline here
将不得不把他的美臀踢出餐厅
is gonna have to kick his beautiful butt to the curb.
但我正搞到一半呢
But I was mid-doing-it!
亲爱的 这里有一股超恶心的臭味
Honey, there's a real funky smell in here.
我得走了
I got to get out of here.
对了 你就住在这里吗
PS, this is where you live?
再给你一百块
Take another $100.
厄尔 好啊
Earl, hi.
麦克斯的心情如何
What kind of mood is Max in?
相当不错
Pretty good.
在她的心情指数表上 现在的值低于微醺
On the Max scale, she's below slightly drunk
但比打飞顾客的值高
but above punching a customer out.
很好
Oh, good.
我还担心她会生我的气
I was worried she'd be mad at me
因为我必须开除她的小白脸
'cause I had to get rid of her boy toy.
卡洛琳 如果我想听故事
Caroline, I'd put my hearing aids back in
我会把我的助听器戴上
if I wanted to hear a story.
猜猜我包包里有什么东西送你
Guess what I have for you in my purse.
我上周要的卫生棉条吗
The tampon I asked for last week?
不是 但再次对那事向你道歉
No, and again, so sorry about that.
真心是我不对
Really dropped that ball.
毛毛虫软糖
Gummy worms.
没错 我夺走了你的糖果美男
Yes, I took away your man candy,
带我买了你爱的那些畅销口味
but I got you these, the hot ones that you like
是从有食品罩那家好糖果店买的哦
from the good candy store with the sneeze guards.
好货啊
Fancy.
别担心纳西特了
And don't worry about Nashit.
我给他找了另一份工作
I got him another job.
帅毛毛虫
Hot worm!
干净的玻璃杯来了
Clean glasses coming through.
奶子不错
Nice rack.
现在我知道为什么男人喜欢对我这么说了
Now I know why guys like saying that to me.
他在那
There he is!
我的新员工
There's the new employee.
阿憨 真不敢相信你会因为麦克斯一句话
Han, I can't believe you would hire someone
而随便请一个人
just 'cause Max asked you to.
这事跟麦克斯或你都没有关系
This has nothing to do with Max or you.
这男孩对我说了一句话
The boy here said something to me
你们俩是无法理解的
that you two couldn't understand.
我说了什么 先生
What's that, sir?
说我是一名勤奋的工人吗
That I was a hard worker?
就这句 没错
That's it! Yes!
天堂的恩赐
Manna from heaven.
我终于有一个干活的员工了
I actually have an employee who works.
醋意大发了吗
Jealous?
这份工作我能做
Now, this job, I can do.
从小我有五个兄弟姐妹
You know, growing up, I had five brothers and sisters,
而我是最不好看的那一个
and since I was the least attractive,
所以碗一直都是我洗
I had to clean all the dishes.
洗碗室见 纳西特
Meet you in the dish room, Nashit.
麦克斯 你这是干什么
Max, what are you doing?
嗨翻天甜点吧或许不准有员工炮情
There may not be hookups at The High,
但在我们的烂到炸餐厅 这个可以有
but there are hookups here at our lowest low,
我们现在就要开搞
and we are doing it.
琳琳好喜欢
Caroline likey.